blinn.edu 2019-12-10

# Privacy Notice | Blinn College

**Web Privacy Statement**

The Blinn College District is committed to ensuring the privacy of personal information. We do not actively share personal information gathered from our web servers. However, because Blinn is a public institution, some information collected from the Blinn website, including summary server log information, emails, and information collected from web-based forms, may be subject to release. This means that while we do not share or sell information unless solicited, in some cases we may be compelled by the Texas Open Records Act to release information.

Blinn College complies with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which prohibits the release of education records without student permission.

The Blinn website contains links to external websites. The College is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of external web links.

**Information We Gather**

The following information may be collected and stored automatically from all users accessing the Blinn website to browse or download information:

• Internet address of computer being used  
• Web pages requested  
• Referring web page  
• Date and time  
• Type of web browser being used

This information is used to occasionally create summary statistics which are used for purposes such as assessing what information is of most interest to users, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to outside (third) parties unless legally required.

**Personal Information You Provide to Us**

Blinn does not retain personally identifiable information about you when you visit its websites unless you choose to provide such information to us (i.e. sending an email, participating in a survey, responding to a request for information or "contact us" form, etc.). We consider any information that could reasonably be used to identify you as "personally identifying information." This includes, but is not limited to:

• name  
• address  
• email address  
• Social Security Number  
• Any combination of data that could be used to identify you such as your birth date, zip code, and gender.

If you provide personal information in an email or by completing a form and submitting it through our website, we may use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. We do not collect personal information from such communications for any purpose other than to respond to you. We do not collect information for commercial marketing.

**Security and Accuracy of Personal and Confidential Information**

Although no computer system is 100 percent secure, Blinn has deployed extensive security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control.

If you are concerned about the accuracy of information contained in your personal records, you should refer to the appropriate custodian of record. 

**Off-Site Links**

Links to non-Blinn organizations are provided solely as a service to our users. These links do not constitute an endorsement of these organizations or their programs by Blinn, and none should be inferred. Blinn is not responsible for the content found at these links.
